babynames.com 2018-12-13

# BabyNames.com Privacy Policy

This site is owned and operated by Moss Gathering LLC, a Nevada Limited Liability Company. 

rev. April 25, 2018

**BabyNames.com** has created this statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting the privacy of our visitors. The following summarizes our information-gathering and dissemination practices for our website.

## Your Personal Information

You may use many features on the BabyNames.com website without inputting any personal information into the website. To become a basic member, we only ask for your e-mail address, a unique username, and password. No other information is required. Registered users may choose to enter more information like first and last name and baby's due date by going to **My BabyNames** in the menu and then **My Settings**. On the My Settings page, you may enter or change your personal information and choose which of these are viewable to the public by clicking on **Privacy Settings**.

## User Profiles

Upon registration, BabyNames.com creates a public user profile page for you. Each part of your profile can be hidden from public view by logging in and going to MY PROFILE and then PRIVACY SETTINGS. The following fields are set to public by default, but can be changed at any time: 

  * Your Profile Picture
  * Username
  * Gender
  * Parent Type/Family Type
  * Interests
  * Online Status
  * Community Title & Badges
  * # Message Board Posts
  * Last Message Board Activity
  * VIP Expiration Date

## Making a Purchase

When you make a purchase on the BabyNames.com, we interface with our merchant provider, Stripe.com. Your name and credit card information is sent securely with encryption to the Stripe.com server. No credit card information is stored on BabyNames.com whatsoever, and is completely unrelated to your BabyNames.com user profile.

## Your IP Address

**BabyNames.com** records user IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, administer our site and identify malicious visitors on the message boards. IP addresses remain private, and are not displayed or posted on the site to any other user.

## Links

This site contains advertising and links to other sites, however we assume no liability and are not responsible for any practices of such third party Web sites, including their privacy practices or content.

## Security

**BabyNames.com** has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information by third parties. We use SSL encryption, firewall intervention, software and hardware redundancy and a comprehensive data backup schedule. Nonetheless, we cannot guarantee the protection of such information against loss, misuse or alteration.

## Opt-In Mailing List

You have the option to add or remove yourself from the monthly newsletter and mailings for special discounts and offers from our partners. We take great care in making sure our users do not receive unwanted email. BabyNames.com sends a periodic newsletter to our members who have opted in to receive it. We will never opt you into our email communications without your permission and we will never sell your information to third parties. IF you receive a special offer from one of our partners, it will always come from our server, as we send them out on the advertiser's behalf. We also ensure that every email you receive from BabyNames.com contains a link to remove yourself from the mailing list. To manage your BabyNames.com email settings, go to our [Newsletter Page](http://www.babynames.com/newsletter/).

## Children's Guidelines

**BabyNames.com** discourages users under the age of 13 from entering any personal information without consent from a parent or legal guardian. **BabyNames.com** does not condone posting or distribution of personally identifiable contact information of any individual, including baby's surnames. BabyNames.com does not entice (by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity) any person to divulge more information than is needed to participate in any given activity.

## Use of Cookies

Like many websites, BabyNames.com stores several cookies on your computer so that we can remember who you are when you return to the site. If you choose to have BabyNames.com remember your login information, that information is stored within your browser software. Your password is encrypted and cannot be viewed or processed by any other person or website. Other cookies include your BabyNames session id, so we can keep track of what names you have voted on. The Google advertising network uses a DoubleClick DART cookie in the ads served by Google on the BabyNames.com website. When users visit our site and view or click on a Google ad, a cookie may be dropped on the user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies enables Google to serve ads based on your visit to BabyNames and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the Doubleclick DART cookie by [visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

## Your Data and Third Parties

BabyNames.com will never share or sell your personal data to any third party without your consent. This includes any identifiable information like your name, email address, or IP address. We may use a third party service provider to conduct our contests, surveys, promotions or special offers, and that company will be prohibited from using our users’ personal information for any other purpose. We will not share the personal information you provide through our contests, surveys, promotions or special offers with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice. 

## Third-Party Advertisers

BabyNames.com allows third-party companies to collect certain information when you visit our web site. These companies may utilize cookies, pixels or other technologies to collect and use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., hashed data, click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit the websites of the [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/) or the [Networking Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices). 

## User-uploaded Photos

BabyNames.com allows users to upload photographs in the Community Message Boards. While uploading a photo, the user agrees that they have rights and permission by the subject and copyright holder to do so. If you have any objection to a user-uploaded photo, please contact [support@babynames.com](mailto:support@babynames.com) with an explanation of the photo and a screenshot, if possible. We will do our best to investigate and remove the violating photograph.

## Removal of Personal Information

Users can have all their personal information, message board posts and images removed by closing their account on BabyNames.com. To easily close your account and remove all your information, click here. Once an account is closed by a user, all of the data is immediately deleted from the BabyNames.com servers and cannot be recovered.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any changes, we will notify you by revising the "Last Updated" date at the top of this page and, in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to our homepage or sending you an email notification). If there are material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you more directly by email or means of a notice on the home page prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to review this page whenever you access the website to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy. If you disagree with any changes to this Privacy Policy and do not wish your information to be subject to the revised Privacy Policy, you will need to delete your account and stop using the BabyNames.com website. Your use of any of the BabyNames.com features after the posting of such changes shall constitute your consent to the changes.

## How to Contact BabyNames.com

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you may contact: [support@babynames.com](mailto:support@babynames.com).

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to BabyNames.com User Support Services department:

**BabyNames.com**  
User Support Services  
P.O. Box 751353  
Las Vegas, NV 89136-1353  
Message Line: (702) 848-5510  
Email: [support@babynames.com](mailto:support@babynames.com)
